grandparents have no respect when they
watch your kids you know that right
they do whatever they want to do and you
can't say anything because you're like
it's free so you just gotta let it
happen
[Music]
they don't care like do placin he has
peanut allergies is gluten allergy
they're like okay I'll make sure I give
him this thing at four o'clock I'll give
him the other thing at seven
I'll give him as soon as you leave
they're like you ain't getting none of
that stuff kid I've raised 7 kids and
they're all fine right you come back two
kids eyes are all swollen like what are
you like hey I raised you and your
brothers and you're alive right that's a
great parents only qualification for
doing a good job is that you're alive
yeah yeah I'm a little messed up
Oh people gotta be stopped at some point
right listen follow me for a second I
wanna be killed or anything okay I just
think they should have to take some kind
of test this up before they buy certain
electronics old people don't know how to
use anything you have it be in line
behind somebody we're over the cell
phone with that stupid default ring on
the whole time don't even know it's them
ringing right
[Music]
[Applause]
now is that my phone why is it like nap
there's a salad button on the cell phone
hit the sella button
my grandmother she's on the phone of
people bragging about me using a remote
control like a child you should see
Corey use that remote control the other
day he changed the channel from another
room
I'm like Nana you could change the
channels too if you stop hitting
auxilary and hit the cable button you
could change the channels to my
grandfather that used the microwave
listen how to use it everything he puts
it a microwave he pushes 43:33 it
doesn't matter what it is pop-tarts
ramen noodles 4333 the other day he came
in the kitchen he was reheating the
fish-and-chip and he had any one of
those white Styrofoam containers yes he
put anything he puts 43:33 I said this
is gonna be good
I like the 15-minute mark the container
just collapsed at the 22 minute mark he
came back in the kitchen he was looking
in the microwave hey that don't look
right
I don't remember putting cheese on that
stuff I said that's provolone cheese
grandpa that's problem
and I watched him me every byte of it -
I don't care he's got to learn he knows
that's not cheese he knows that
styrofoam what kind of cheese you cut
those wooden ketchup in pepperoni see
you'll hear that cheese squeaking he
said I thought that was my cell phone
ringing I said see
watch my entire special for $0.99 oh
just watch more clips check out more
clips click one of them you gotta check
it out now if I were you I'd probably
click the $0.99 one cuz that goes right
into my pocket click one click it click
it click click lick lick lick lick lick
lick lick lick lick lick lick lick lick
lick okay